<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Deck</title>
    <description>The Deck is a repository of my thoughts, rants and musings.&lt;br&gt; I am The Deck.
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 17:54:13 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 17:54:13 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Restless</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Please, meet my new Apple Watch app: &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/restless-never-fall-asleep/id1048930054?l=fr&amp;amp;ls=1&amp;amp;mt=8&quot;&gt;Restless&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/201711/app_icon.png&quot; alt=&quot;Restless app&quot; class=&quot;center-image&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The app helps you stay awake when you really need to: 
&lt;br /&gt;
when you’re driving late at night coming home after a party, when you want to pull an all-nighter to work for those midterms … etc.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It works by using the Apple Watch haptic feedback to keep you focused. You’ll receive a nudge regulary and when you’re heart rate is seemingly shows that you’re on the verge of falling asleep.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can check it out on the App Store:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/restless-never-fall-asleep/id1048930054?l=fr&amp;amp;ls=1&amp;amp;mt=8&quot;&gt;Restless - Never Fall Asleep !&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Nov 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/11/20/Restless.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/11/20/Restless.html</guid>
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple set to expand Siri</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Stephen Nellis &lt;a href=&quot;http://www.reuters.com/article/us-apple-developer-idUSKBN18T30A&quot;&gt;writing for Reuters&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Apple Inc (AAPL.O) is expected to announce plans next week to make its Siri voice assistant work with a larger variety of apps, as the technology company looks to counter the runaway success of Amazon.com Inc’s (AMZN.O) competing Alexa service.&lt;br /&gt;…&lt;br /&gt;
Currently, Apple’s Siri works with only six types of app: ride-hailing and sharing; messaging and calling; photo search; payments; fitness; and auto infotainment systems. At the company’s annual developer conference next week, it is expected to add to those categories.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No shit Sherlock !&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2017 00:00:00 +0200</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/06/03/apple-set-ta-expand-siri.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/06/03/apple-set-ta-expand-siri.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>iBooks &quot;edge case&quot;</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Michael E. Cohen, &lt;a href=&quot;http://tidbits.com/article/17053&quot;&gt;writing for TidBITS&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;iBooks is not quite as unreliable and confusing as it was when I wrote about it last year, but neither has it improved nearly as much as loyal iBooks users deserve. Moreover, what little support documentation Apple provides is sketchy and inaccurate, leaving the impression that even the support and documentation departments within Apple are ignoring iBooks.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Federico Viticci, commenting at &lt;a href=&quot;http://tidbits.com/article/17053&quot;&gt;MacStories&lt;/a&gt; about the previous quote:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Cohen’s library may be an edge case with over 700 titles, but the problems he mentions are basic usability issues that should get fixed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As the developper of an &lt;a href=&quot;http://librairie.cubesoft.fr&quot;&gt;iOS app to manage your ebooks library&lt;/a&gt;, let me tell you that 700 ebooks is &lt;em&gt;far&lt;/em&gt; from an edge case. A quick query in my stats showed me that the &lt;em&gt;average&lt;/em&gt; number of ebooks per active user in Librairie is 1134. This makes total sense when you think about it: people using this kind of apps are serious about managing their whole books library and are voracious readers.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As most Apple apps, iBooks is designed for casual users. The ones who will buy a handfull of ebooks in the iBooks Store and don’t even know what an ePub file is. If you’re an ebooks power user, &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/librairie-ebook-cloud-reader-epub-mobi-azw3/id742022507?l=fr&amp;amp;ls=1&amp;amp;mt=8&quot;&gt;I have a solution for you&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 20 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/02/20/ibooks-edge-case.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/02/20/ibooks-edge-case.html</guid>
        
        <category>ibooks</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Two Mac universes</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://mjtsai.com/blog/2017/01/31/it-just-works/&quot;&gt;Micheal J. Tsai&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Adrian Kosmaczewski (via Andy Lee):&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I start iTunes. It tells me that I need to log in to Apple Music. I do not remember ever having logged off. I enter my username and password. The dialog goes away. iTunes still does not allow me to listen to music. I close and re-open iTunes. I log off and on a few times. I finally reboot my Mac. I discover that the artist I would love to listen to that morning is not available on iTunes Music. I select another artist. I hit play. Music does not come out from the built-in speakers. I plug in my old 2002 Harman Kardon SoundSticks. I plug the USB 3 to USB dongle first.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I sit on my Mac and open a Pages file stored on iCloud, one I was working on my iPad Pro during the weekend. The sync fails and I cannot see the last modifications I made on my iPad Pro. Open and close apps on both devices. I reboot them both. Pages for Mac tells me that there is a conflict between the versions in both devices, even though I have never edited the file on the Mac. I select the version on the iPad. My changes are lost.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;[…]&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;blockquote&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;I try to open an application I bought yesterday on this Mac. The operating system protests, telling me that I have to login to the App Store because the application was bought in another Mac. It is not true. I log in anyway. The app opens.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This seems too bad to be real, but I’ve had days recently that feel like this. I have an old Mac and sometimes think a new one would be more reliable, until I read about problems people are having with a brand new MacBook Pro and display. At least I don’t have kernel panics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And at the same time, in a slightly parallel universe &lt;a href=&quot;https://sixcolors.com/post/2017/01/apples-record-quarter-by-the-numbers/&quot;&gt;Jason Snell reports at Sixcolors.com about the latest Apple quartely results&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Mac unit sales weren’t a record, but because of rising average sale prices (thanks, MacBook Pro!), &lt;strong&gt;Mac revenue set a record&lt;/strong&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;May be because people are buying new Macs hoping they’ll be more reliable ?&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/02/01/two-mac-universes.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/02/01/two-mac-universes.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Commit DB version 1.3</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Commit DB, the arguably &lt;a href=&quot;http://commit.cubsoft.fr&quot;&gt;best iOS MySQL client&lt;/a&gt; on the market 😉 has a new version. Besides a few bug fixes, the main new feature is the ability to use &lt;em&gt;SSL to secure your MySQL connections&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy coding !&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 31 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/01/31/commit-db-1-3.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/01/31/commit-db-1-3.html</guid>
        
        <category>projects</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Apple will let developers reply to reviews in the App Store</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Benjamin Mayo, writting for &lt;a href=&quot;https://9to5mac.com/2017/01/24/apple-will-let-developers-reply-to-reviews-in-the-app-store-soon-for-ios-and-mac-apps/&quot;&gt;9to5mac&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Apple has announced that it will soon let developers reply to reviews on the iPhone, iPad and Mac App Stores. As part of the iOS 10.3 release notes, the company says that by the time iOS 10.3 is available to customers, developers will be able to respond to customer reviews on the App Store.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;This is a major breakthrough enhancement as developers have been asking Apple for better ways to interact with customers for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I see a lot of pushback from the developers community this morning along the lines of: “the App Store will now be your public support channel”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It might be a problem but I see at least two reasons that it may be a good thing overall:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;Good and empathetic support will reflect positively on your app (of course, &lt;a href=&quot;https://marco.org/apps&quot;&gt;if you provide no support, that might be a problem&lt;/a&gt;). I know it seems naive but I really think it will go a long way with the core users of your apps, the ones that buy already knowing what it does and want it to work rather than bash the dev for making them pay a few bucks.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;
    &lt;p&gt;If you want Apple to listen to us and (hopefully) implement more substantive changes to the store we really ought to have a constructive attitude to the changes they’re making right now. Sure, many implementation details will probably suck at first but we have to show Apple that they’re right to not be content of the status quo.&lt;/p&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 25 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/01/25/apple-will-let-devs-reply-to-reviews.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/01/25/apple-will-let-devs-reply-to-reviews.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding the UTI of a PEM certificate on iOS</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;UTI stands for “Uniform Type Identifiers”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s like the definition of a file type tying together files extensions, mime types and higher level UTIs.
In iOS (and macOS also I guess) you have to provide UTI(s) to initialize the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;UIDocumentMenuViewController&lt;/code&gt; class, also known as the “iOS Document Picker”. This list will tell the system which type of files your Document Picker will be allowed to open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is all good and well unless you don’t know which UTI to use for the file type your looking for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was trying to import pem certificates into one of my apps and didn’t know which UTI to use for this task. Fear not, fair developer, Apple said ! Head to our official list of &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/library/content//documentation/Miscellaneous/Reference/UTIRef/Articles/System-DeclaredUniformTypeIdentifiers.html&quot;&gt;System Declared Uniform Type Identifiers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, no declared UTI covered my use case. Or so I thought …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having wrestled with this issue for the better part of the day I have at last found this &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; useful site: &lt;a href=&quot;http://uti.schwa.io&quot;&gt;UTI type browser&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s the UTI list that Apple should have provided. There are much more types available than the one listed in the official Apple documentation. Including the one I needed:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;public.x509-certificate
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/01/04/uti-of-a-pem-certificate-ios.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/01/04/uti-of-a-pem-certificate-ios.html</guid>
        
        <category>coding</category>
        
        <category>iOS</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>App Transport Security enforcement delay</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=12212016b&quot;&gt;Apple developper news&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;App Transport Security (ATS), introduced in iOS 9 and OS X v10.11, improves user security and privacy by requiring apps to use secure network connections over HTTPS. At WWDC 2016 we announced that apps submitted to the App Store will be required to support ATS at the end of the year. To give you additional time to prepare, this deadline has been extended and we will provide another update when a new deadline is confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is disappointing for the developers who had put in the effort necessary to make their apps comply with ATS. However, I suspect that Apple realized that there are just &lt;em&gt;too many edge cases&lt;/em&gt; to really enforce this rule as is.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/12/22/App-Transport-Security-enforcement-delay.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/12/22/App-Transport-Security-enforcement-delay.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        <category>coding</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Raining On My Parade</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Mark Gurman reporting for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-12-20/how-apple-alienated-mac-loyalists&quot;&gt;Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Mac fans shouldn’t hold their breath for radical new designs in 2017 though. Instead, the company is preparing modest updates: USB-C ports and a new Advanced Micro Devices Inc. graphics processor for the iMac, and minor bumps in processing power for the 12-inch MacBook and MacBook Pro. Cue the outrage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, &lt;a href=&quot;http://thedeck.fr/2016/12/20/mac-desktop-sign-of-life-finally.html&quot;&gt;that was quick&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/12/21/raining-on-my-parade.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/12/21/raining-on-my-parade.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mac desktops sign of life, finally</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Tim Cook in an internal memo reported by &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2016/12/19/apples-tim-cook-assures-employees-that-it-is-committed-to-the-mac-and-that-great-desktops-are-coming/&quot;&gt;Matthew Panzarino at TechCrunch&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The desktop is very strategic for us. It’s unique compared to the notebook because you can pack a lot more performance in a desktop — the largest screens, the most memory and storage, a greater variety of I/O, and fastest performance. So there are many different reasons why desktops are really important, and in some cases critical, to people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The current generation iMac is the best desktop we have ever made and its beautiful Retina 5K display is the best desktop display in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some folks in the media have raised the question about whether we’re committed to desktops. If there’s any doubt about that with our teams, let me be very clear: we have great desktops in our roadmap. Nobody should worry about that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was it so hard, Apple ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just acknowledging that your desktop line is still alive ? In my opinion, a lot of virtual ink would have been saved about the new MacBook Pros if they had said it earlier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, this doesn’t mean that we (“pro” users, whatever that means) are out of the woods the just yet. It may just be an iMac speed bump in the spring for all we know. But still, it feels much better than the void we’ve been living in for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a related note, I thought a bit more about the end of the Apple branded monitors: I now think that it is sign that we will never see again (in the foreseable future at least) a screenless Apple desktop. It’s one thing for Apple to send its customers to LG for a secondary display used with a laptop. It a completly different one to release a brand new machine that &lt;em&gt;cannot&lt;/em&gt; be used without an add-on sold by another company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mac Pro and the Mac Mini won’t probably ever be updated again in their current form. Brace yourself for some kind of iMac Pro.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/12/20/mac-desktop-sign-of-life-finally.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/12/20/mac-desktop-sign-of-life-finally.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
