<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Deck</title>
    <description>The Deck is a repository of my thoughts, rants and musings.&lt;br&gt; I am The Deck.
</description>
    <link>http://localhost:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 17:43:23 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 17:43:23 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v3.1.6</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Finding the UTI of a PEM certificate on iOS</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;UTI stands for “Uniform Type Identifiers”.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s like the definition of a file type tying together files extensions, mime types and higher level UTIs.
In iOS (and macOS also I guess) you have to provide UTI(s) to initialize the &lt;code class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;UIDocumentMenuViewController&lt;/code&gt; class, also known as the “iOS Document Picker”. This list will tell the system which type of files your Document Picker will be allowed to open.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is all good and well unless you don’t know which UTI to use for the file type your looking for.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I was trying to import pem certificates into one of my apps and didn’t know which UTI to use for this task. Fear not, fair developer, Apple said ! Head to our official list of &lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/library/content//documentation/Miscellaneous/Reference/UTIRef/Articles/System-DeclaredUniformTypeIdentifiers.html&quot;&gt;System Declared Uniform Type Identifiers&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Of course, no declared UTI covered my use case. Or so I thought …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Having wrestled with this issue for the better part of the day I have at last found this &lt;em&gt;very&lt;/em&gt; useful site: &lt;a href=&quot;http://uti.schwa.io&quot;&gt;UTI type browser&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s the UTI list that Apple should have provided. There are much more types available than the one listed in the official Apple documentation. Including the one I needed:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;public.x509-certificate
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 04 Jan 2017 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2017/01/04/uti-of-a-pem-certificate-ios.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2017/01/04/uti-of-a-pem-certificate-ios.html</guid>
        
        <category>coding</category>
        
        <category>iOS</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>App Transport Security enforcement delay</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://developer.apple.com/news/?id=12212016b&quot;&gt;Apple developper news&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;App Transport Security (ATS), introduced in iOS 9 and OS X v10.11, improves user security and privacy by requiring apps to use secure network connections over HTTPS. At WWDC 2016 we announced that apps submitted to the App Store will be required to support ATS at the end of the year. To give you additional time to prepare, this deadline has been extended and we will provide another update when a new deadline is confirmed.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is disappointing for the developers who had put in the effort necessary to make their apps comply with ATS. However, I suspect that Apple realized that there are just &lt;em&gt;too many edge cases&lt;/em&gt; to really enforce this rule as is.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 22 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/12/22/App-Transport-Security-enforcement-delay.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/12/22/App-Transport-Security-enforcement-delay.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        <category>coding</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Raining On My Parade</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Mark Gurman reporting for &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2016-12-20/how-apple-alienated-mac-loyalists&quot;&gt;Bloomberg&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Mac fans shouldn’t hold their breath for radical new designs in 2017 though. Instead, the company is preparing modest updates: USB-C ports and a new Advanced Micro Devices Inc. graphics processor for the iMac, and minor bumps in processing power for the 12-inch MacBook and MacBook Pro. Cue the outrage.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, &lt;a href=&quot;http://thedeck.fr/2016/12/20/mac-desktop-sign-of-life-finally.html&quot;&gt;that was quick&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 21 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/12/21/raining-on-my-parade.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/12/21/raining-on-my-parade.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mac desktops sign of life, finally</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Tim Cook in an internal memo reported by &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2016/12/19/apples-tim-cook-assures-employees-that-it-is-committed-to-the-mac-and-that-great-desktops-are-coming/&quot;&gt;Matthew Panzarino at TechCrunch&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The desktop is very strategic for us. It’s unique compared to the notebook because you can pack a lot more performance in a desktop — the largest screens, the most memory and storage, a greater variety of I/O, and fastest performance. So there are many different reasons why desktops are really important, and in some cases critical, to people.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The current generation iMac is the best desktop we have ever made and its beautiful Retina 5K display is the best desktop display in the world.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Some folks in the media have raised the question about whether we’re committed to desktops. If there’s any doubt about that with our teams, let me be very clear: we have great desktops in our roadmap. Nobody should worry about that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Was it so hard, Apple ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Just acknowledging that your desktop line is still alive ? In my opinion, a lot of virtual ink would have been saved about the new MacBook Pros if they had said it earlier.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now, this doesn’t mean that we (“pro” users, whatever that means) are out of the woods the just yet. It may just be an iMac speed bump in the spring for all we know. But still, it feels much better than the void we’ve been living in for a long time.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On a related note, I thought a bit more about the end of the Apple branded monitors: I now think that it is sign that we will never see again (in the foreseable future at least) a screenless Apple desktop. It’s one thing for Apple to send its customers to LG for a secondary display used with a laptop. It a completly different one to release a brand new machine that &lt;em&gt;cannot&lt;/em&gt; be used without an add-on sold by another company.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Mac Pro and the Mac Mini won’t probably ever be updated again in their current form. Brace yourself for some kind of iMac Pro.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 20 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/12/20/mac-desktop-sign-of-life-finally.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/12/20/mac-desktop-sign-of-life-finally.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Nervermind Apple</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I just wanted to take advantage of one of the coolest looking feature of watchOS 3 : the auto unlocking of your mac.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Well, the first step is to enable &lt;em&gt;2 factors authentification&lt;/em&gt; for your iCloud account. My account was already on the &lt;em&gt;2 steps authorization&lt;/em&gt; scheme so that should be a piece of cake, right ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Wrong, so f***ing wrong.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You first have to downgrade your account to go back to the classic protection by security questions. By doing so, macOS asked me to create a new user because I used my iCloud account to log into my mac and for some reason that was not possible anymore.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Okay … I guess ?&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;At this point I had no real choice anyway so let’s go ahead : create a new password and that’s it, you have your new user identical to the previous one (or so it seems, keep reading …).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then upgrade your iCloud account to &lt;em&gt;2 factors auth&lt;/em&gt; : Oh boy ! There’s nothing that makes me like doing my taxes more than a good old fashioned self imposed Apple nightmare …&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;When you activate &lt;em&gt;2 factors auth&lt;/em&gt; you have to validate each device you use (iPhones, iPads, Macs) with a second factor. This second factor being (it’s the only option) a prompt that appears on one of your trusted devices. The problem being that each of my devices were then asking for a validation and that none of them was showing me the said prompt.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So what can you do ? After several reboots, logout / login again cycles … you give up. That’s for sure what I did. I reverted my iCloud account back to security by &lt;em&gt;security questions&lt;/em&gt; (because of course the &lt;em&gt;2 steps verification&lt;/em&gt; scheme is not available anymore once you have &lt;em&gt;upgraded&lt;/em&gt; to &lt;em&gt;2 factors auth&lt;/em&gt;).&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And now, the kicker: remember my macOS account that &lt;em&gt;seemed&lt;/em&gt; OK. Well it was not. The session password was now de-synchronized from the FileVault password that I have to provide at each reboot to decrypt my hard-drive. So each time I rebooted I had to enter the FileVault rescue key.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Had I not set a FileVault rescue key (which would have been stupid sure, but what if you’ve lost it ?) trying to unlock my Apple Mac with my Apple Watch through my Apple iCloud account would have nixed all my data.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Let that sink in.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;So thanks Apple and next time would it be possible to … No, you know what, nevermind. It’s on me.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Next time I won’t even try.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 15 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/12/15/nevermind-apple.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/12/15/nevermind-apple.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Mac Niches</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;http://mjtsai.com/blog/2016/12/12/which-macs-are-people-using/&quot;&gt;Micheal J. Tsai&lt;/a&gt; speaking of the mac models used by the users of its macOS apps:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;The numbers for the MacBook seem really low to me. The 2% (1.68% before rounding) includes both the MacBook One and the plastic MacBook that was discontinued in early 2012. The 12-inch MacBook never seemed attractive to me—overpriced and underpowered, not to mention the keyboard—but I would have expected to see more people using it. 
&lt;br /&gt; […] &lt;br /&gt;
It’s frustrating that Apple sees the MacBook One as a worthwhile niche but doesn’t want to make a high-end MacBook Pro with a larger display, more RAM, a real keyboard and trackpad, etc.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some niches seem more comfy than other in the new Mac ecosystem.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/12/13/mac-niches.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/12/13/mac-niches.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Change font size in screenshots created with Frameit</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/fastlane/fastlane/tree/master/frameit&quot;&gt;Frameit&lt;/a&gt; is a very nice utility to create nice looking App Store screenshots. It will take your images, add a device frame around them and optionaly a title of your choosing in multiple language. In short, it’s a godsend.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;But unfortunatly, as any tool, it has a few shortcomings. One of them (for my use case at least) is that there’s no way to choose the size of the font you’re using for your titles.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;For example, look at this screenshot for my app &lt;a href=&quot;https://itunes.apple.com/us/app/librairie-ebook-cloud-reader/id742022507?mt=8&amp;amp;at=1010lrXT&quot;&gt;Librairie - Ebook Cloud Reader&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/201612/screenshot_bad.png&quot; alt=&quot;Bad screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s not bad per se but it could be much better with a bigger font to add some punch. The corresponding json is:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-json highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;        &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
            &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&quot;filter&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;collection&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
            &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&quot;title&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
                &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&quot;color&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;#bc1626&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
                &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&quot;text&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Automatically sync and read all your ebooks stored in the cloud&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
            &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The trick is to make Frameit think that the text will take more space and as a consequence use bigger font to fill that space. For this, you can use a new line character in your description. The &lt;em&gt;Framefile.json&lt;/em&gt; becomes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;div class=&quot;language-json highlighter-rouge&quot;&gt;&lt;pre class=&quot;highlight&quot;&gt;&lt;code&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;        &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
            &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&quot;filter&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;collection&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
            &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&quot;title&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;{&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
                &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&quot;color&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;#bc1626&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
                &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;nt&quot;&gt;&quot;text&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;:&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt; &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;s2&quot;&gt;&quot;Automatically sync and read all\nyour ebooks stored in the cloud&quot;&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
            &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
        &lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;p&quot;&gt;}&lt;/span&gt;&lt;span class=&quot;w&quot;&gt;
&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And the rendered screenshot:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/201612/screenshot_good.png&quot; alt=&quot;Good screenshot&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Et voilà !&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 06 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/12/06/Change-font-size-screenshots-created-with-frameit.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/12/06/Change-font-size-screenshots-created-with-frameit.html</guid>
        
        <category>coding</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Amazon introduces Lex</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Yesterday, Amazon introduced a new service in beta called &lt;a href=&quot;https://aws.amazon.com/fr/about-aws/whats-new/2016/11/introducing-amazon-lex-now-in-preview/&quot;&gt;Lex&lt;/a&gt;:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;blockquote&gt;
  &lt;p&gt;Amazon Lex is a service for building conversational interfaces into any application using voice and text. Lex provides the advanced deep learning functionalities of automatic speech recognition (ASR) for converting speech to text, and natural language understanding (NLU) to recognize the intent of the text, to enable you to build applications with highly engaging user experiences and lifelike conversational interactions. With Amazon Lex, the same deep learning technologies that power Amazon Alexa are now available to any developer, enabling you to quickly and easily build sophisticated, natural language, conversational bots (“chatbots”).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In a nutshell, this is a Siri competitor available for all developpers. And instead of being limited to the handfull of intents that Apple provides (and won’t extend until at least next year iOS major version) you can use it for whatever use case you want. You can even use text to talk to this “assistant” an often asked feature for Siri.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Obviously the drawback is that you won’t be able to invoke it from outside your app. Still that seems massively interesting.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/12/01/amazon-introduces-lex.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/12/01/amazon-introduces-lex.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        <category>siri</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Paris&#39; Passerelle Simone de Beauvoir</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;For those who have liked the &lt;a href=&quot;http://kottke.org/16/11/chinas-lucky-knot-bridge&quot;&gt;Lucky Knot Bridge&lt;/a&gt; posted by Kotke this morning I humbly present la passerelle &lt;em&gt;Simone de Beauvoir&lt;/em&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/201612/simone_de_beauvoir.jpeg&quot; alt=&quot;Passerelle Simone de Beauvoir&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This bridge is located in Paris and links the 13th district (on the left bank of the Seine river) with the 12th district (on the right bank). It was opened in 2006.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Paris is a beautifull city, more modern than what one might imagine.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Dec 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/12/01/Paris-passerelle-Simone-de-Beauvoir.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/12/01/Paris-passerelle-Simone-de-Beauvoir.html</guid>
        
        <category>paris</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Hit where it hurts</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Speaking of which, HP is trying to capitalize on the current backlash against Apple among its pro users:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/images/201611/HP-store.png&quot; alt=&quot;HP Store&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The screen capture is in french, for some reason I couldn’t get the english version. It says that “Pros are moving from the Mac to HP”. And they’re giving a few testimonials of video peoples.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 22 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://localhost:4000/2016/11/22/1-hit-where-it-hurts.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:4000/2016/11/22/1-hit-where-it-hurts.html</guid>
        
        <category>apple</category>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
